[music]
All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful Wednesday afternoon. God bless
everybody in the name of Jesus Yeshua
the Messiah. I pray you are all very
blessed as the Bitcoin price, guys, is
well on its way to new all-time highs,
baby. Man, these glasses are looking
pretty crazy, aren't they? These are
some crazy looking glasses, man. These
are the weirdest looking glasses I've
ever seen in my life. You know, I wear
these glasses all the time when I'm
trying to trade. You know what I mean?
Because I can see the charts right
through the glasses. [laughter]
You know, I wear these when I'm supposed
to be paying attention to my wife. She's
like, "Jason, I just want to talk, you
know, Jason, I I just need to talk, you
know." I'm like, "Don't worry, babe. I
love listening to you talk. You know, I
love talking. You know, us dudes love
that. So, I put on these glasses, right?
I look right into her eyes,
you know, but all I see are those juicy
blue and purples, baby. All I see are
those juicy blue and purples,
you know. By the way, click the link in
the description to get your own wife
glasses.
They also work for anybody else who
wants to talk to you.
All right. And for you kids still in
school, you can wear them in class. Your
teacher will never know. Nothing
suspicious about these glasses. I'll
tell you that much. They're way better
than the old ones I used to use. All
right.
Now, the question is,
are we going to pop
or not? That's the question. And I am in
a uh revenge long here from yesterday.
Quarter million dollar long. Still in
the million dollar short here over on
Bitbase. still in the quarter million
dollar long over here on
Antarctic decentralized exchange. Links
in the pin comment description for
Bitbase. Giving away $500 every single
week. Also guys, big shout out to
Blowin. We're going to do a $2,000
giveaway today.
A VIP. I have to be a VIP, but we're
going to do the VIP giveaway today
courtesy of Blofin.
But you can see here, Bitcoin is Chop
Chop City. Chop Chop City. and we need
to discuss the reality of the situation.
Are we going to see 67,000 or is the top
end is this whole thing a giant bull
trap? Today's the day we answer all
those questions and more. So sit back,
relax, buck your seat belts because
we're about to answer everything you
wish you knew about crypto right here on
the Jason Casper YouTube show. Welcome,
welcome, and God bless. Welcome,
welcome, and God bless. Now, as we know,
the Bitcoin price is coming up to none
other than this very crucial level here,
the top of the sideways range that we've
been trading since basically June,
right? This is the June range. And so,
if we can reclaim this level, 67,000, we
we have a straight shot, a straight shot
all the way to the mid70s. All right. If
we put on our volume profile here, you
can see that if we reclaim this very key
white line, it's going to be a quick
move. If we flip the chart upside down,
it will be a smooth move. We're talking
Taco Bell at 1:59 a.m. since they close
at 2 a.m.
You're eating Taco Bell plus White
Castle plus oatmeal, plus prunes, plus
brand flakes, plus a fiber supplement,
plus popcorn. Lots of it. Boom.
straight down to dump city, baby. Of
course, this is an upside down chart.
All right, otherwise the Taco Bell late
night analogy doesn't work.
But you could see how easily that could
happen. We got to give a major shout out
to everybody in the chat right now.
First of all, a big shout out to
Preparing for War. Shout out to CBK
Wahoo.
Shout out to DL O'Brien 3673 and get
M9Q. Shout out to Baja 2 and rookie own
who says top equals in. Shout out to R
Pink the blue unblockers. Shout out to
Pashit Sharma. God bless you. Shout out
to Joanie HSV
who's in 10th grade. You're in 10th
grade. Oh my goodness. I remember when I
was in 10th grade. It seems like a
thousand years ago. Shout out to Dark
Pai.
Music is your friend from Europe.
Shout out to Jesse Gellick holding it
down with the wrench. Shout out to
Darren does things
and Mr. Arouge
and Randy NLA. We finally tapping 67
today. Shout out to Crypto for Columbus
One. God bless, bro. Good to see you.
Probably on Tilt. New for Ammy 433
wants to know long or short. Well, the
answer right now is yes.
I got a little bit of a both. A little
bit of both on here. I got a little bit
of boat. A little bit of boat on here
right now.
Oh yes. Yes. I got a little bit of both
on here. Yes. Yes, I do. Got a little
bit of boat. I got a little bit about a
little bit of boat.
Shout out to Patrick Schuner.
Where to take entry at current price or
wait? Look, let's discuss. Let's pop
into the chisnarts,
you know.
Let's pop into the Chisnarts. Let's see
here.
Uh, okay. So, here we go, guys. We're
popping into to the dang chisnarts.
And here are the charts, guys. Long
story short,
we are at a crucial level. However, we
did tap the dollar into this PC, and
that's not the best look for Bitcoin.
Actually, you know what's strange? It
looks like we've had a little bit of
value area shift here. And depending on
how we pull this value area volume
profile,
[sighs]
it looks like we actually front ran it
here on the daily. So it's it's really
like the the jury is still out about
whether or not we hit this level or not.
And so let's discuss like what what is
probable possible to happen. We do have
some strange news here. All right,
Donald Trump is threatening to blow up
power plants or bridges in Iran. That's
definitely not the best
uh news for the market, but we do have
money flowing in on the ETFs.
Let's take a look at the overall picture
here. Weekly time frame, twoe time
frame. In about 11 days, we will confirm
a bullish divergence. The weekly has
already confirmed a bullish divergence.
All right. Um
and give the context of confirmed
bullish divergence on the weekly. I
mean, that's a pretty bullish sign. the
daily time frame. Not only has it had a
confirmed bullish divergence
where the price gets lower as the
momentum waves [music] get higher,
but we've also just seen our first money
flow cross here. So, when you have a
bottom, a nice looking bottom, a juicy
looking bottom like this, big on the
left side, nice and juicy, and then the
right side is very skinny. And the
personification of the right side is
this woman right here. All right. Did
you know this woman is herself a skinny
butt cheek? The whole woman is the
skinny butt cheek. All right, but the
skinny woman herself has skinny butt
cheek. It's like a fractal. It's like a
fractal. All right, you zoom out on the
weekly time frame, you see the big juicy
left cheek, the skinny right cheek. You
zoom in on the right cheek. The more you
zoom in, all of a sudden, boom,
you see the fractal playing out within
the skinny cheek herself
are more uneven butt cheek pattern, a
bullish pattern. This is exactly what we
see on the chart, right? We go to the
weekly time frame, we see an uneven butt
cheek pattern. We zoom into the daily,
right? We look what's happening in this
cheek on the right cheek itself. Boom.
Within the right cheek is another uneven
butt cheek pattern. Okay? When you have
this
and then you get a money flow cross,
that next trigger wave typically tends
to give you a higher move. So, what does
this mean? It means I'm looking at this
range here.
I'm looking at this range right here.
scoop doop floop where even if we get a
big pullback here and even if we rip
through all this liquidity to the
downside, I would actually be looking
now to back test this value area low and
[music] get a trigger wave here on the
daily time frame. And if you get that
with as the money flow is getting even
if we curve back into the purple a
little bit, guys, that could give us a
pretty powerful pump. All right, a PPP,
a triple P as we call it in in Casper
land. All right, a PPP.
All right, a triple P.
And that could take us back up to the
top of the range. But the question is,
are we even going to get a pullback? So,
let's take a look. We're going to go to
the 4hour time frame. And we understand
we're coming to local resistance. We do
have a 4hour trigger wave printing here.
Money flow is getting lower.
All right. So, it's actually not the
most bullish looking chart locally, but
here's what I would say. Here's what I
would say right now. I'd say that if we
pull
we pull a local fib from the last swing
low to the high, you can see that our
golden pocket and our 786 is coming in
right around the very important back
test of the local PC and the value area.
So for me, if we're going to come down
and get a bounce from here, we could
actually see something like this, which
would allow us to get something like
this, which then could give us a nice
top. For some reason, I just feel like
we're going to tag this this high here
at least. I I feel like 68K could very
well be in the cards because a lot of
people are looking at 67K and even front
running 67K as a short. And although it
could very well be, I just feel that the
bearish divergences would look much
nicer if we actually got a local bounce
and then came up for one more high. Now,
of course, if we come up for one more
high and then we flip this into support
now, then all that bearishness kind of
fades away into the into the past
because once you flip 67,
you know, let's call it 675 into
support, the highest probability is
we're going up to the mid70s. All right,
so that is absolutely what could be
happening here. You could see based on
this uh trade I'm in now, right, that uh
yeah, potentially I am looking for that
move up to the mid70s. Let's check this
here. This other trade I'm in right now.
You know, you got in the long on a
retrace. Um
Google earnings are are announced today,
says Randy NLA.
[music] Um do I still have the 66K
short?
I don't know. I have a short from CS
666.
666 right here.
Yep, it's still open. 666 still open,
guys. All right.
Still open. The reason why I took this
long trade from here, I took it this
morning in the Casper Crew VIP New York
Open live stream where we give the
trades in the moment, guys. All right.
In the Casper Crew VIP, we give the dang
trades in the moment. All right. The
reason why I took it is not because I
think it was the best trade in the world
to take, but it was simply because we
had bullish divergences on the 24-minut
time frame, the 12-minute time frame as
we were coming down to test the previous
week high. All right, so this is the
previous week high, we come down, right?
We get the bounce and we are printing
bullish divergences here on the 24-minut
time frame. So, I figure, you know what,
what the heck, you know, I accidentally
closed out of a long trade yesterday.
Let me see if I could get a little
something something from this one. Let
me see if I can get a little something
something. Right. [music] So, so far I
have a little something something. A
little something. I was up almost two
grand on this before with this wick, but
who knows? Maybe I get wrecked. I don't
know. I don't know.
All right. I don't know. But that is why
I took that trade there.
Um
Jesse Gell says, "My laptop is finished.
I've been trading my ass off the past
week. I need a new laptop.
Oh, I know. I know how you feel about
that. Sometimes when you're trading so
much on your laptop, you're eating on
your laptop, you're taking it into the
bathroom, you know, there's a splash
from the toilet bowl onto the keyboard,
and then, [music] you know, you need a
new one. You know what I'm saying? You
know what I'm saying? Um, [snorts]
yeah. So this long could play into
something. It could turn into something
more. We we do have a change of
structure here like very locally we have
our higher lower lower higher lower
higher lower low. That made a higher
high you know maybe make a higher low
and squeeze this you know this kind of
[music] bullishness. We are seeing
market cipher B starting to curve back
to the upside here. So that is very
possible. So, I'm very curious to see
what happens at $67,000
because if we flip into support, well,
big big move to the upside. And if not,
then big big move to the downside. Um,
it's been a messed up rise. Wreck
shorts, wreck longs, wreck shorts, rinse
and repeat.
What price do I expect the next peak to
be? Um,
shout out to not quicker.
um
of the actual bull market, the next bull
market. I I expect the the between 150
and 180,000. I I'm really not expecting
very much for the next bull market,
guys. I I was talking about it this
morning in the VIP. Someone asked, is it
a good time to buy Bitcoin? You know,
objectively speaking, guys, it is a good
time to buy Bitcoin. Like, if you're on
the sideline, you have no Bitcoin. We
are literally right now from from the
high, we are at a
48% discount. All right. Basically 50%
off any asset that you want to buy in
life. If you have the opportunity to buy
that thing at half off, you take the
opportunity,
right? It's a great opportunity. And
even if we're cons if we're considering
a $150,000 Bitcoin next cycle, which is
very conservative in my opinion, that's
still over, you know, you're doubling
your money.
You know, as a 1.3x,
that's a lot. That's a lot. If you
invest in something and you more than
double it over the course of a few
years, that's a lot. Now, let's say we
come up towards 180. All right,
$180,000. That's a 1.7.
You know, it's almost a 2x. That's
That's pretty good.
You know, that's pretty good, right?
So, you know, I I' I'd say that yeah,
objectively speaking, it's a good time
to buy. I'm not expecting too much for
the next bull run. I'll be honest with
you. Um, the reason why is because when
we just look at the diminishing returns
of these bull runs, [music] you know,
the reality is in 2015 to 2018, 12,000%
gains, 12,000%.
Then from 2018 to 2021 from 12,000% to
2,000%.
Then last time from from 2,000% to 700%.
And so if if we do bottom out just
around 40k like I'm thinking and we come
up to, you know, 150,000 that's like
300%.
I'd say that's that's that's pretty
good, you know, that's pretty pretty to
be expected, [music]
you know. But but who knows, you know,
maybe this time is different like
everyone likes to say. But the sad
reality about Bitcoin is, guys, is you
know, and the sad reality about crypto
too, this is a sad reality. like the
whole the whole concept of you know
just your average guy in his mom's
basement becoming a millionaire
overnight in crypto in Bitcoin should I
say like those days are over man those
days have not we haven't seen those days
since 2020 and 2021 was the last time
you you realistically without like
gambling on some stupid you know [__]
coin
last time really to make life-changing
money was back in the in the 2020 2021
bull run where we saw pretty much every
altcoin go crazy and Bitcoin 2,000%
gains. [music] You know, the sad reality
is now in this industry, those
opportunities are are probably gone,
right? There's going to be the gems here
and there and there's going to be money
to be made for sure, but that crazy easy
money is no longer. So, you know, the
the the smart thing to do now, honestly,
for those of us who have made it this
far in crypto, and we're here for the
money,
not for the technology. Let's be clear
here. We're here for the money. We're
not here for the technology. I don't
give a crap about blockchain technology
or the future of money. Because the
reality is blockchain technology and the
future of money is is 100% going to be
used to enslave humanity to the point
where you might not even be able to buy
gas. in a certain uh outside of a
certain radius of your house, right? You
might not be able to buy meat because
your carbon footprint's too big with the
digital currency. All right? This stuff
isn't going to set you free. It's going
to put you in bondage. So, I'm here for
the money right now. All right. The best
thing we can do is is just learn how to
play the cycles and slow and steady wins
the race. Tortoise in the hair type
stuff, you know, nice and slow on the
treadmill. 2.5 mile per hour walk. All
right. Here we Oh, we're up $700. You
know what I'm saying? We're up $700,
baby. Um,
the only thing says, "I love you, Jason.
I think I have to get you a Ugandan
woman as a reward." That's the strangest
thing I think I've ever That's the thing
the strangest thing I ever heard in my
life,
you know. [music] That's the strangest
thing I ever heard in my life. J Boy
Bullish says
he's
J Boy Bullish. I don't think I can read
that, bro.
Um,
yeah. Still long for the morning. Yes,
Senor. I'm still on for the morning even
though you told me to wait, bro. And I
could have taken profit, too. But you
know what, Senor? Sometimes in a man's
life, he just has to. He has to do what
he has to do. And in this case, I have
to do it, man. I have to do it. All
right. I appreciate you looking out for
me, though.
Um, can we check Sana? Yeah, we we could
check Sana. Just real one last thing
about Bitcoin here, guys. I hope we come
down into our box, this green box here.
In fact, really, I would like this box
to come down a bit lower like [music]
this. This is kind of where I would
prefer our bottom to be in in the fall,
right? In the fall,
>> [music]
>> um, around o the end of September, the
beginning of October.
And I know we have a confirmed weekly
divergence, which we never had before,
but I just have a hunch.
I just have a little bit of a hunch that
we're going to see history rhyme again
here because every single time since
2014,
it's been the time and the retracement
[music]
every single time. So, this is why I'm
kind of holding out. And I'm one/ird
into Bitcoin right now. But objectively
speaking, if I was in a different
position in my life, I might act I would
pro potentially be more into Bitcoin now
just because I've recognized the fact
that a 50% move to the downside that
that is a good price to buy objectively
speaking. You know, it's so crazy to
think about all the people who are like
considering buying Bitcoin here because
we're making new all-time highs and
considering buying here because we're
making new all-time highs and
making new all-time highs. It's like,
you know what? when you're in a bull
run. Okay, if we're making all-time
highs, you kind of missed the boat, bro.
You should have been buying at the green
box, right? So, you know, now we know
we're not buying the all-time high. It's
50% discount. That's a big discount.
And so, yeah, if we do come down a
little bit more, just for the record,
that would be another
40% if we hit the 786.
That's a That's a lot more money to be
made on on the Bitcoin on the OB BTC,
baby. Yeah. $66,000
on the dollar.
$66,000 on the dollar right now. Here's
one last thing, guys. If the Bitcoin
price falls through my first green box
of hope and wonder,
then we're coming down to green box
numero dose of hope and wonder, which is
basically taking out all this liquidity
and coming to this zone here at the
bottom of the range. I would still be
bullish if Bitcoin retests 60K.
And the reason why is simply because
we have a really nice looking bottom
here. So, we get our shoulder, our head,
our shoulder, and then we could come up
back to 67K or potentially mid70s, but
we'll have to cross the bridge when we
get there.
All right, we'll have to cross the
bridge when we get there. And speaking
of bridges, your boy DT DJT
uh is threatening to blow up bridges or
power plants.
Uh which is not necessarily the most
bullish thing when we're at resistance,
right? When you're at resistance, we're
trying to blast off and go the distance.
When uh the orange man starts starts
typing stuff on on Twitter, it it it
could it could it could lead to some
volatility.
All right. Could lead to some
Um,
but is this time different? This time
could be different. You know, this time
could be different.
Mr. Daddy Engineer, yesterday I was more
bearish. Are you kidding me, bro? I
literally spent half an hour
recuperating from my stupid decision to
close a long trade because I'm bullish.
I mean, go and watch yesterday's stream,
man.
Um, but look, the difference here is I'm
talking macro versus micro. All right?
When I'm on the weekly chart, I want to
see Bitcoin dip down. I want to see
these lows taken. I I want to make
another low. I want to dip down lower.
If I'm on a lower time frame, you have
to understand, it's all about what time
frame you're on. All right? If if we
reclaim 67K on the local range, we come
up to here, right? Doesn't mean we don't
drop down to here, right? That doesn't
mean that. But when we're looking at the
short-term time frame, we have to
recognize if we reclaim 67.5,
that is extremely bullish given the
context of bullish divergences on the
two week, the weekly, the daily, and the
4hour, the money flow cross on the
daily, and the flip of resistance into
support. However, given the larger
context and the 4-year cycle and where
we're scheduled to bottom out, right? In
that case, then we would want more
downside here. So, we could get in at a
lower price, right? When it comes to
trading, you have to understand, you
could be long and short at the same time
and be right. I do it all the time. You
could be short on a small time frame
looking for a scalp trade while you're
long on a swing trade. You could be
short on a swing trade and be long on a
day trade. The price never goes straight
up or straight down. What the price does
is it finds a sideways range in multiple
time frames, right? So, for example, we
have this sideways range right here.
It's pretty clear, right? A clearly
defined high, a clearly defined low, a
clearly defined high, a clearly defined
low, right? But within this, we have
this sideways range with clearly defined
highs and lows. We have this sideways
range with clearly defined highs and
lows. We have this sideways range with
clearly defined highs and lows. We have
this sideways range with clearly defined
highs and lows.
We have this sideways range right now
with clearly defined highs and lows. You
zoom in even more and guess what? We
have this range right here with clearly
defined highs and lows. We had this
range up here with clearly defined highs
and lows. We had this range here with
clearly defined highs and lows. So it's
like pick your time frame and you can
have different biases based on your time
frame. And once you understand that it
unlocks
I don't know like freedom freedom when
it comes to trading. You don't really
care as much about what the price is
going to do cuz there's opportunity
everywhere. All right. If you want to
learn more check out my free
trading course. All right. Go to my
YouTube channel. Go to my YouTube
channel. go to the Jason Casper free
trading course. All right, I have 18
sessions here for free
that explain exactly how to do it. And I
actually I recommend check out the how
to manage open trades section
>> where I talk about all this kind of
stuff here for free. And I'll be honest
with you, man. I'll be honest with you.
People charge thousands of dollars for
less information. This I'm giving it
away for absolutely for free. Free.99,
baby.
free.99.
You know what? If an asteroid dropped,
would Bitcoin drop? Yeah, that that
could be the the black swan event, bro.
Uh, you know, that could be the black
swan event.
Can someone be straight and gay?
Uh,
never really thought about that.
Uh, what if America drops a nuke on
Iran? Will Bitcoin be affected? Yeah.
Yeah, Bitcoin would be affected by that.
Yeah. I mean,
here's the thing. Um,
there could be a a black swan type event
that would that could give us the big
move to the downside on Bitcoin and that
would be the bottom. So, the more
catastrophic, not that I wish any
catastrophe on anybody. I don't I don't
wish any catastrophe on anybody. The
reality is, you know, there are there
are crazy people in this world that will
do crazy things and those crazy things
affect the market. And often times when
there is a catastrophic event,
what it does is it wrecks people in the
short term, but it makes people lots of
money in the long term. All right, 911
is a great example of that. 2008 [music]
housing collapse is a great example of
that. COVID 19 is a great example of
that. Not just in Bitcoin, although the
Bitcoin is the most famous one, but look
at this. I mean, COVID 19, you saw
Bitcoin drop 72%.
Only to pump up,
1700%.
You know, and you could look at like the
S&P 500. So, if anything crazy like that
happens, when you know that you're near
the bottom of the four-year cycle
and something crazy happens,
that is not a sell signal, guys. That is
not a sell signal. It's really hard to
keep your emotions under control when
you saw Bitcoin down at $3,000 in 2018.
Finally, next year, things are finally
picking up again, guys. Finally picking
up again. and then the whole world shuts
down and oh my goodness, we're back down
at the exact bottom. It's hard to keep
your cool. All right, but if we get
something crazy happening and Bitcoin's
down here, oh my goodness, that's an
opportunity. It's an opportunity. It's a
risk that I'm willing to take personally
because, you know, the way I look at it
is this. If I buy down here and the
whole world really is over, the whole
world really is over, then oh well, who
cares? The whole world's over. It
doesn't really matter anyway. But if
things continue, inevitably we're going
to come back. You know what I'm saying?
So it's like either we're all screwed
and at least you bought the bottom,
right? You could say, "Hey, I went broke
buying the bottom." At least you're not
the guy who went broke buying the I went
broke buying the bottom.
You know, I wouldn't mind being the guy
who goes broke buying the bottom.
That's why Birkshshire Hathway is
currently sitting on 10 billion in cash.
Seriously,
would it affect Bitcoin if aliens attack
the Earth? Yes. Yes. If there is, fullon
disclosure, it will affect the Bitcoin
price. Maybe that's the black swan
event, right? Maybe that's the Who
knows? Like, who knows? We can't really
know. That's what makes it a black swan.
And the more people think about the
possibilities, it means it's less likely
that that's actually going to happen.
You know what I'm saying? It's less
likely it's actually going to happen if
people are talking about it and thinking
about it. especially
if someone ever makes a YouTube video
about it and it spreads around in the
conspiracy
uh community, you know for certain it's
not going to happen.
That's just how it works. Nobody's
prepared for a black swan. You can't
prepare for a black swan. If you think
you're prepared for it, they're going to
come out with a different black swan.
That's just how it works. You know what
I'm saying? Uh the whole effing crypto
market is still recovering from 1010 and
you still think another black swan is
coming. By now lows are in maybe. Uh but
yeah, no I I it is possible that the
lows are in but I've already told you
why I don't want the lows to be in yet.
All right. Um
I I you know
if they started calling them white
swans, would that affect the market? No.
It would just highlight the systemic
racism that plagues our culture, my
friend. That's about all it would do.
All right, let's take a look at
Ethereum.
Um,
so you know what I have to say here,
Etherum, guys.
I don't see, and I was talking about
this before, but do I do I want to be
bullish on ETH? I don't want to be
bullish on ETH, but but here's my
running hypothesis with ETH right now.
All right, my running hypothesis with
ETH is this. a few months before Bitcoin
topped out. Now, remember, Bitcoin
topped out on October 6th. So, this is
the high for Bitcoin. But what happened
was approximately
approximately, let's let's get a let's
get a measuring device on here. 50 days
before, all right, Ethereum tops out.
All right, Ethereum tops out. So, now
Ethereum is bottoming out. you know,
let's say that I mean 50 days later,
we're pretty much that's that's going to
be at the end of August, right? But if
we stretch it out maybe a 100 days or
so, like maybe ETH bottoms out before
Bitcoin and maybe we see something like
this. Maybe we see ETH flip market
structure on the weekly, come to back
test and then do something like this.
This would actually be really nice
for ETH because this actually is a
pretty nice bottom considering the fact
that we are making a higher low with a
bullish divergence, bullish money flow
on the weekly.
The two week has a really nice fat
oversold wave. The 3-day
and it's got some bullish divergence
here. Nothing too crazy, but it's got
something.
You know, the daily looking pretty nice.
it it I don't want to be bullish on ETH,
you know, I want I want everything to
hit new lows here. But the fact is we
are reclaiming the macro PC going all
the way back to 2020,
right? So we literally have 6 and 1/2
years, well about 5 and 1/2 years of
price action here. We're reclaiming the
high volume. So, I would say this like
same with Bitcoin. If I did if I wanted
to buy ETH, I I would be buying some now
be because we're down 70%. Well, we're
down 60%. 60% from the all-time high.
That's a pretty good discount. And we're
heading into the beginning of
a a bull cycle, right? the the last
quarter of 2026, 2027, 2028, 2029,
[music] I believe, is going to be
bullish for crypto, right? So, it's not
like we're buying randomly here,
although this was a great place to buy
um back in April 2025. That was a great
place to buy, but
you know, if I was looking to load up,
and I'm not I'm personally not. I have
all the ETH I want, but it's not
necessarily the worst place to get in
considering we're we're reclaiming uh
resistance. What would I really like? I
would love to see ETH drop down below
1300 right now because we have the
liquidity here from 2023 March. We have
the liquidity here from April 2025. We
have liquidity here as well.
Man, it would be nice to scoop up some
ETH if we do if we do get a black swan
event and it does make a lower low. It
would be nice to scooch some up in this
area. But
here's the one thing we need to keep our
eyes on for ETH. If we actually do make
a higher high than this, that is
officially a change of market structure
on the weekly. That is officially
entering into a bullish trend. That's
$2,500.
This is something that really does mark
the a major change. Okay, a major change
changing market structure on the weekly.
If we do that, you would have to expect
the higher low to come in, right? you
would have to expect a higher low to
come in. If we make a higher high here,
you would expect then this to turn into
more of an accumulation range before
eventually we go back for the highs,
right? So, this is looking pretty
interesting here on Ethereum.
Um,
if it comes out that Elmo is on the
J list,
I don't even know what that is to be
honest.
October 10th was a gift. Man, a lot of
people got wrecked on that day.
Honestly, ETH is trash, says Jesse
Gillick. I mean, I I I I'm I'm going to
maintain bullish on ETH, bro. You know
that the fact that people hate ETH so
much in my opinion
just points to the fact that it's
probably going to start to rip and
people are going to feel like they
missed the boat.
[music]
I think it's it's probably going to
start to rip and people going to feel
like they missed the boat.
Uh
I have bowling bowls. Boy says I have
bowling bowls
in my shoulders.
Is that what they call them in China?
They call them bowling bowls.
Bowling bowls. You know,
>> have I heard about the giant celestial
object orbiting directly in front of the
sun? I don't know. I don't take any of
that stuff seriously. I'll be honest
with you. I don't take any of that stuff
seriously.
Um, you know what we are going to do?
Uh,
we are going to do a $2,000 blow fin
giveaway today.
Okay. Bowling bowls. That's what they
That's what they have in China. Okay.
That's what they have in China.
They probably use those to eat wonton
soup, right?
I have no idea what Chinese people
really eat. I'll be honest with you. If
you're Chinese, let me know what you
actually eat, right? Cuz I know for
certain it's not what American people
call Chinese food. I know Chinese people
don't actually eat that. That's the
whole joke. That's the whole joke, you
know.
Um,
Vitalic Buterine is shredded. That's why
I'm 100%. Yeah, all stables are on ETH.
It's going to pump for sure. Yeah, I I
could see ETH pumping.
I I could see ETH pumping. 98% of alts
are trash. Yeah, ETH is not just any any
old altcoin, though, you know. Shout out
to Jay Armo in the chat.
Yeah, I forgot to check soul. No, I
didn't forget. I didn't forget to check
soul. Here we are. Soul Lana.
All right. So, look, we're coming down.
We're we're we're trying to we're
flirting with this support resistance
flip here.
We have a we have a confirmed weekly
divergence here. We have a confirmed
twoe divergence here.
You know what I mean? It looks pretty
bullish. I'm not going to lie. the fact
that we are printing bullish divergences
here. Unless we pull a Cardano, unless
all these altcoins pull Cardanos
where the bullish divergences literally
mean nothing. When was the last I mean I
guess yeah we had a bullish h
you know what Cardano didn't really have
a twoe divergence.
We did have a oneweek divergence here.
Do you remember this? I mean this this
unless we pull a Cardano and even if we
do pull a Cardano this is looking pretty
good honestly right that weekly did did
give us some G juicy action
but yeah soul's looking pretty bottomed
out as well at a key support resistance
flip you know the $78 level we dip down
to 60
um yeah so I'd say it's the same as
Ethereum though if we can change
structure here make a higher high
then I'd say why not look for a higher
low that would look like a nice start to
look like a nice accumulation.
You know that that would be the real the
real ticket to bullish city on all these
[snorts] altcoins is changing bearish
market structure into bullish market
structure. You know where we we have
clear swing high, swing low, swing high,
swing low, swing high, swing low, swing
high, swing low. If we make a higher
high with these bullish divs on these
multiple time frames, you know, I don't
I don't see why we couldn't come back up
to,
you know, assuming that alts are dead
forever, which I don't think they are. I
don't see why we couldn't come back up
to 175.
A conservative target. A more liberal
target
would I mean, that's a pretty
conservative target.
A more liberal target would be like 200.
You know, we have the golden pocket and
the support resistance flip. A more
liberal target, you know, but I I like I
like to use the conservative target. You
know what I'm saying? You got to make
sure that you have maximum absorbency on
at all times. You can be more confident,
be more assertive, you know, compared to
the the the liberal targets. The liberal
targets, you're more likely to get
wrecked. Um cuz you know, no one really
respects you if you're out in public
looking like this. But there's the
chance that you make more money. All
right. There's the chance that you make
more money.
But
but yet but yet Oh man.
Did you hear liberal Target? Yeah, we're
talking about the store.
The Target is a pretty liberal store. I
think they have
I think they have transgender bathrooms
at Target. They don't really.
Have I tried coffee? Boy wants to know.
I have tried it, my friend. I have
tried. I have tried.
Uh, feal matter machine. If feminism
gets its way, how prosperous would the
world become?
Well, we'd have lots of breast milk.
Wait, no, we wouldn't.
I don't know.
Um, shout out to Helicopter Painter.
God bless you, Helicopter Painter.
You respect the handlebar mustache only,
says Kirk Patrick. Thank you. All right.
You know what? Yesterday we did give
away $1,500.
U, but you know what? We do have to do
we have to do some more giveaways today.
We have to do some more giveaways today.
We are going to do
a a blow fin giveaway today, [music]
but it is
we're going to announce the winners on
this stream right here.
All
right. You know what we're going to do?
We're going to announce the winners
[music]
just so everyone knows. And Blowin's
going to be giving away
$2,000 next week also. Right.
Blowofin is going to be giving away
$2,000 next week also. If you're in the
VIP Discord, enter the raffle and I'm
going to announce the winners right now
to see who has won. By the way, you
know, this morning we just gave away
$500 via Bitbase
and um every single week in here we're
giving away, you know, hundreds of
dollars like on these raffles in the
Casper crew. So, right now, let's see
who wins. Four people are going to win
$500 on Blowofin. The way you win on
Blofin is you have to post your P&L.
All right. Over here in the Blofin
channel, Blofin has custom P&L cards for
Jason Casper. I mean, who wouldn't want
to see their profit and loss with this
face? You know what I'm saying? Look at
that. Look at that. Who wouldn't want to
see their P&Ls looking like this? you
know. So, if you have your custom Jason
Casper P&L,
you can enter into the raffle
to win
money. I think we're doing it every
single month, right? We're giving away
$2,000 a month in here. So, let's see
who wins right now.
Let's see who our winners are.
And if you want a chance to win,
uh, you could sign up to Blowpin.
And if you want a chance to win on
Bitbase, you can sign up to Bitbase.
All right. It's drawing the winners.
We're going to see who our four winners
are. Let's see.
All right. So, these are the winners.
Congratulations to our winners. Congrats
to our wieners. Our wieners. [snorts]
What did you win?
Probably until still warrior triple7. an
invalid name and VA.
Congrats, guys. Congratulations.
Both free members and VIP can join the
Blowpin. Yeah. So, you don't have to be
VIP. You just have to be in the Discord.
The free Discord [music] or the VIP
Discord. All right.
So, sign up to Blowofin, get in the free
Discord, and every month you're going to
have a chance to win. All right.
That's how we're doing the giveaways
now. All right.
Your brother got fired from Target for
having a negative opinion about pride.
Interesting. That's strange. I kind of
thought everyone at Target faked it. I I
you know, I'm still, you know, cuz I
live in such like a like a I feel like I
feel like there's no such thing as
liberals in real life. Feel like it's
just like
feel like they're all AI,
you know?
or just like or just like the media is
liberal. I've never really met a liberal
in real life. That's how that's how
padded I am out here, you know? I don't
see anybody.
But I guess they're real. I guess
liberals are real.
But they won't be real for long, right?
They don't have kids. They chop off
their testicles and all this kind of
stuff. They suck out their uh fallopian
tubes and chop off their mammary glands.
So
pretty soon honestly I mean the thing is
pretty soon they're not going to be
around.
What is Vra? Taka.world is shilling a
coin in here. Taka.world.
He deserves the hammer, says Jose. Yeah,
I think he does.
Yeah, I think you do deserve the hammer
taka. I'm going to ban you myself, bro.
[snorts] But God bless. Where can you
find find the free Discord? The free
Discord is in the description
of the Let's see here video. So, I think
you got to go to
uh any Jason Casper video
and in the description [music]
there's the uh the free Discord right
here. join my free Discord,
you know. Hey, look, Jason Casper's
live.
Jason Casper's live. Guys should check
it out, you know. You should check it
out.
Good old Jason Casper.
All right. Golden Child confirms they're
real. Okay. Okay.
Do I own a pair of Crocs or am I a
normal sandals guy?
Um, I actually don't wear sandals or
Crocs. I did used to have a pair of
shoes that was made by Crocs, but
honestly, right now, I've been wearing
these shoes only or barefoot or or
barefoot shoes. I have barefoot shoes
that are grounding shoes, but if I'm on
the treadmill, I've been wearing these.
All right. There's chicken poop uh stuck
to the bottom of them.
Well, I've been wearing these. All
right.
Ortho feet shoes.
I get them from Amazon. They're
comfortable. They feel good on your
feet. You know, also I wear Sketchers
walking shoes, but the Sketchers walking
shoes, they wear out too quick. They
start to hurt my back. You know what I'm
saying? Why is gold pumping
when Bitcoin and ETH are pumping?
I'm not sure.
We could take a look at gold. Um,
I don't have bullfoot shoes, you know.
I'm sorry. What's my first TP for this
short? Um,
uh, I It's yet to be determined,
honestly. It's yet to be decided on this
one. It's yet to be decided. Here's the
thing. This short was originally a hedge
against my long.
Um, and it technically still is a hedge
against my long. So, I'm I'm long from
from down here, right? And I've closed
like in the last few
trades I've taken here. Like I've closed
quite a bit of money, right? In the last
few, you know, let's say like $95,000
minus. So, like 85 grand I've closed
here in the last few trades. I still
have this trade open here. All right. I
still have this trade open. Plus, I also
just closed out
this trade
for 57 grand by accident, right? Minus
4, so we'll call it 50 grand. So, like
we're up 130 grand in the last few
trades. I'm not in a rush to take
profit. All right. If if it just so
happens that we dump like crazy, I'm not
in a huge rush to take profit because I
have 21 $28,000 of unrealized profit
here that will go away in the event of a
dump.
And so I'd rather have the open short.
All right, I've already locked in 130K,
give or take, right? Over 100K. I've
already locked in. So I can I'm in the
position now where I can just kind of
wait and see what happens. And if one of
these trades gets stopped out, if the
short gets stopped out, you know,
whatever. If the long gets stopped out,
whatever. But because I'm long from the
bottom, right, I'm not really looking to
take profits on this short trade unless
it's really like my longs are about to
get closed out. And by that time, I'll
be up 30K on the short trade, right? So,
I'm just kind of waiting to see what
happens because I'm in that position
[music] to do so. If I wasn't in that
position,
the first place I would like to take
profit on this short would be around
$61,000 because ideally if we are going
to get a bit of a rejection from here,
ideally what I would like to see is I I
would like to see this is confusing.
What is actually going on right now? Oh,
I see that. Was that a Look at this
glitch, guys. Do you see this glitch?
Look at this.
Huh. Ideally, I would like to see this
end up giving us a a retracement so that
we can get long again from around 6160K.
And that would be my first like real
take profit. Take all this liquidity
out. Of course, the other place to look
for a TP1 is coming back to back test
around $65,000 support resistance flip.
Ideally, like for me, if this was the
only trade I was in and I was looking at
it as more of a swing trade, $61,000 is
a really nice take profit on that. You
know what I'm saying? Um,
I dumped the market with that close. I
know, man. I can't believe I did that.
Honestly, h I was watching that this
morning, too. like just reliving the
pain. Why do I do that? Why do I relive
the pain? Why do I relive the pain?
And 50. So that that's that's about
>> Oh man.
Oh my goodness.
How do we do this here? Oh. Oh my
goodness. I can't believe I did that. I
can't believe I did that. Let's Let's
relive the pain a little bit. Oh man,
this is terrible. I'm like, how do I do
this? I'm I'm like, I think I should
take profit. How do I even take profit?
There's like a new interface over here
on Bitbase,
you know.
Yeah, I think I'm going to I think I'm
going to take a little bit of profit
right here. Let's see. Oh, [music] let's
see. Oh. Oh, look. I'm about to hit
market close. And and and I didn't
realize that I had all $546,000
ready to market close here. I I didn't
see this because typically
typically I'm closing my trades like
this, right? If it's on list, right, and
you hit market close, right? It will ask
you how much do you want to close,
right? It will ask you how much do you
want to close. If you have it on details
for YouTube streaming sake to look cool
with all your big position sizes and
take profits, right? Then it's already
set up for you right here. And I didn't
realize this cuz I was too stupid. Like
I wasn't paying attention. I'm live and
all this stuff. And so I just hit market
close thinking it was going to ask me
the question.
Oh.
Ah.
How do we do this here?
Oh no. Did I just close the whole trade?
Oh no. I just closed the whole trade.
Just relive it. Relive it. Relive it.
Relive it over and over again. Oh, it's
terrible. It's horrible.
Man,
that's what I get for trying to look
cool on the internet, guys. That's what
I get for trying to look cool on the
internet. Trying to be sensational.
Trying to be sensational. You know,
that's what I get. That's what I get,
you know.
Shout out to Trader Gio in the house.
God bless you, man. Guys, make sure to
hit up, make sure to subscribe to
Trader. You have these same tank tops.
These are the best tank tops ever.
Honestly, I have this weird AI camera
that follows my face wherever I go.
These tank tops, this brand right here,
whatever brand this is, I love them. You
could wear them. They can get sweaty.
They can get gross.
All right.
And then they're dry the next day. You
could wear them all week and your wife
doesn't even know. Usually, if you wear
a con t-shirt and you try to wear it all
week, your wife, she says, "Jason, get
the heck out of here. Get out of here.
Change your clothes. Take a shower." You
wear these. They could be soaking wet
with sweat after the live stream. But um
but within a few hours, your wife's
hugging you. She's like, "Oh, Jason, you
smell so good. Thank you for changing
your clothes for me. You're like, "No
problem, babe." And of course, you put
on your your wife [music] glasses so
that she can talk to you and you can
pretend to listen, but really you're
looking right at those candles.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Thank you for
sharing your feelings. You say, "Thank
you for sharing your feelings. I really
appreciate that." You know,
you have to get the nod and down. She's
talking to you. You're looking right at
the candles. She thinks you're looking
right at her cuz you can kind of see
your eyes through these glasses,
you know. Oh yeah. Oh wow. Oh, that's
crazy, babe. You know
what? What's up with girls and women?
Why do women always want us guys to take
showers? You know what I'm saying? Why
do girls always want guys to take
showers? What the heck, man?
You know
why do you ladies always want your men
to take showers? Don't you know we
thrive in the grime?
>> You know what I'm saying? Um, shout out
to Trader Gio.
No freestyle today.
Um,
shout out to Dusty Hunt in the chat.
Yeah, showers are overrated.
Dave Digger doesn't know, but he heard
girls go first cuz they're the worst.
Real men don't take showers. I I'll
never forget when I was in high school,
I had a teacher named Mr. McCcluskey.
Mr. McCcluskey. He actually had to uh he
got punched in the face during fight.
He tried to break up a fight. He got
punched in the face and uh he had to he
couldn't come back for
couldn't come back for the rest of the
year. And then we had teacher named Mr.
Shall after that. Mr. McCcluskey told us
he never wore deodorant and he thought
it was gay. And we, all of us dudes, us
10th grade dudes, we thought to
ourselves, gay? That's not gay. How are
you gonna attract the ladies if you
smell bad? I didn't understand back
then. You know, I didn't understand the
power of the sweaty pits. You know what
I'm saying? He said, "I never wear
deodorant. It's gay." That's what he
said.
But he got punched in the face. He got
punched in the face. He never came back.
And then our substitute teacher, Mr.
Shallabi, [music] he was such a cool
guy.
Because
what he did, man, he was a funny guy. He
told us a scary story. He said, "I'm
going to tell you a ghost story. It's
real scary. It's real scary." He had all
the kids gather around him, like in a
circle all around him, right? And he's
like, "Come. You got to come close. If
I'm going to tell this story, it has to
be like campfire style." So, everyone's
like on their desks all circled around
this dude telling the
tell he's telling this story. And he
he's a good storyteller, let me tell
you. Everyone's focused in on the story.
This was so funny. What a troll this guy
was. The story gets real intense.
They're in this house. All this crazy
stuff is going on. And then they get to
a part where they're about to open a
door where something real intense is
going on the other side. And he's like,
and he's like, and he tells everyone to
come in real close. He's like, I open
the door
and then he gets real quiet and
everyone's really like listening on the
edge of their seat. All of a sudden, he
just goes, he like screams at the top of
his lungs and like jumps up and
everyone's like, "What?" Everyone
totally freaks out. Everyone's super
startled. He's like, "Gotcha."
That was hilarious. [music] Good old Mr.
Shall. Am I offering a student discount
for the VIP?
I don't know how to do that. I don't
know how to verify that.
Deodorant is gay. Lesson of the day. Is
deodorant gay? I don't know. That's what
I learned in history.
Mr. McMusty.
Uh-oh. We have a fiveminute head and
shoulders.
Let's check out the five minute. Let's
check out the one minute.
Oh, hang on. Let me get to trading view.
You call this a head and shoulder? I
mean, maybe. Maybe that's a head and
shoulder. I don't know. I don't know
what the heck this is, man.
Head and shoulders, knees and toes.
Was
Mr. Was Mr. McCcluskey married? The no
deodorant guy? I don't know. I don't
know. But I don't wear deodorant and I'm
married. [music] All right. So, I feel
this guy now. You know, hopefully I
don't get punched in the face by a
student trying to break up a fight. It's
a good thing I'm not a teacher. Speaking
of not being a teacher, check out my
course where I'll teach you how to trade
for free.
It's free on my YouTube channel. What
kind of music is this? This is like some
smooth jazz.
Let's see if we can find anything.
I I do like this playlist a lot.
Some tracks are a little bit too smooth.
Nah, he didn't fart. That would have
been funny, too. But he scared the crap
out of everybody.
>> Everyone else farted.
Oh, you're right. I'm a homeschool
teacher. I hope I don't get punched in
the face when my kids are fighting.
I think most of us punch a teacher in
the face. I never punched a teacher in
the face, you know. Thankfully not.
Thankfully not. You got expelled for
doing that in my school. And I'm glad I
didn't get expelled. I got suspended
many times. Many times.
I got suspended so many times. Oh man, I
did so many strange things. This one
time, I dressed up like a clown. I ran
into my friend's math class and I
grabbed the chalk. I started running
back and forth on the chalkboard saying
la
drawn chalk all over back and forth.
Then I got up on the desks. I ripped my
shirt off.
I said, "Thank you very much." And I ran
out. Got suspended for doing that. What
else did I do?
This one time I put Chinese food in a
whole bunch of random places in the
library. I don't know why I did that. I
don't know why I did that.
I just thought it would be funny.
Wouldn't it be funny if there's just
like Chinese food in random places? Put
it all over like this computer all over
the books. I don't know why I did that.
That was crazy. I got suspended for
that. What else did I do? I got
suspended so many times by accident,
too. This one time I jumped up to touch
the ceiling like kids do and
accidentally cracked the ceiling tile in
half. It fell down. Got suspended for
that. What else did I do?
I think I got in like one fight, got
suspended. Wasn't even like a real
fight.
Uh
I don't know. I would I was always
suspend but never expelled, you know.
Didn't want to get expelled.
[music]
Did I have a bit of the tism in school?
Yeah, I I feel like I definitely have a
bit of the tism. I'm very socially
awkward. I can't look you in the eye. If
this is real life, I wouldn't be able to
look you in the eye.
You know, I'd be wearing my trading
glasses,
you know.
Do I think we'll get to 80K before 67?
Uh, I hope so, man. I hope so. I hope we
get to the mid70s. That would be nice.
We're getting a little bit of a juicy
green candle of hope right here.
You dropped out before they could
suspend you. Now, that's that's good. I
I wish I had done that flat smack. See,
here's the problem with me in high
school is I didn't want to let my
parents down. I love my parents. I
didn't want to let them down. So, I
tried real hard not to get in trouble
and not to get ex, [music] you know,
suspended and all this cuz I wanted to
graduate high school to make my parents
happy. Ironically, I never did. I did. I
never did.
I never did. I never did graduate. So, I
should have just I should have just got
expel. I should have just punched that
teacher in the face. No, I'm joking.
Nah, my teachers were all cool. I I was
cool with all my teachers. I was super
cool with all my teachers, you know.
But
you hope we get to 40k before 80k. I
hope we do something crazy. If you send
me an ID, I suppose Joanie HSV, here's
the problem, man. All of a sudden,
everyone's going to have an ID. All it
takes is chat GBT. Hey, bro. Let me get
a student ID. Then all of a sudden
everyone's a student. I don't know. I'll
have to figure out a way to make it
work. We'll see if we can do it. We'll
see if we can do it. All right. We'll
see if we can do it.
Oh, okay.
Lord have mercy.
Oh crap.
Oh crap. Oh no. Oh, we're in the red.
No, we're back in the green, baby.
Discord
video call. Yeah, I guess so. Shout out
to Trader Gio.
Well,
well, um, what's what what does Jason
Casper always say? Right. [music] When
the trade starts to go against you, you
got to end the stream immediately.